<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coursera on WHW blog</title>
    <link>https://mattwang44.github.io/tags/coursera/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coursera on WHW blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mattwang44.github.io/tags/coursera/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Note: Cloud Engineering with GCP on Coursera</title>
      <link>https://mattwang44.github.io/2020/06/15/gcp-ace-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mattwang44.github.io/2020/06/15/gcp-ace-note/</guid>
      <description>This is the note of the course Cloud Engineering with GCP. Go to this article to see how I prepared for GCP ACE exam.
Mind Map     GCP  Network Resources  VPC  Network Subnet IP   Load Balancer  HTTP(S) SSL Proxy TCP Proxy Regional Multi-Regional   VPN &amp;amp; Peering &amp;amp; Interconnect   Compute Services  Compute Engine (GCE)  Disk type  persistent  HDD/SSD   Local SSD   Instance template Instance group   App Engine (GAE)  Standard Flexible   Kubernetes Engine (GKE) Cloud Function   Storage  Data warehouse  BigQuery   Database  NoSQL  BigTable Cloud Firestore  Datastore mode Native mode     Relational  Cloud SQL Cloud Spanner   Redis/Memcache  Cloud Memorystore       SDK  gcloud gsutil bq   Stackdriver  Monitoring Logging Debug Error reporting Trace   Big data services  BigQuery Cloud Dataproc Cloud Dataflow Cloud Pub/Sub Cloud Datalab       SDK  Cloud SDK installation and quick start gcloud tool guide gcloud command gsutil command bq command  Resource Management  Resource Hierarchy  Global  Images Snapshots Networks   Regional  External IP addr.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>